Hello friends, welcome to your own
YouTube channel PBS Coaching Center. Friends,
if you are one such, that is, a Common Service
Center operator, then there is good news for you.
Friends, another new service life has been launched in Pune,
which will provide a lot of treatment and
you will earn a lot from it from the morning. So,
let's start and find out
which is the new service life in Pune. But
before that, if you are new to this channel, then
you are requested to subscribe to the channel
because from here you keep
getting news every moment, so that
you get the first information about any government scheme. So, let's
start and find out
which new service has come in CHC. A
[music]
Do it.
Hello
friends, to know about the new service that has come in CHC, first of all
you will
log in to your digital service portal.
After logging in, you will come here to the news service, then
you will see
Border
Security Force. You have to register in it
and you will get a good income. In this, you will
work in a very good service office of
Border Security Force and
you will have to register in it,
but right now, nothing in detail about this service.
No, as soon as the details are available,
I will tell you and even before this, a new
service had gone live whose name was Digital
Police, which is being shown here, so both the
services have come which are very good, you should
work in both of them, Digital Police and
Border Sacrifice, both are very good
services and if you work in this, then you will earn a
very good income, so let's
meet again in the next video, till then,
thank you, Jai Hind, Jai Bharat, Jai Bhim friends.